http://www.projectinsight.net/legal/privacy-policy

Project Insight Privacy Policy
Effective as of February 7, 2018, Project Insight has updated our privacy policy. For a prior version of our privacy policy, click here.
Project Insight (collectively, "Project Insight" or "Metafuse" or "Metafuse, Inc." or "we" or "us" or "our") complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States.
Project Insight has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles.
If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/
In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Project Insight commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Project Insight at:
Project Insight
Attn: Privacy Officer
230 Commerce, Suite 285
Irvine, CA 92602, United States
privacy@projectinsight.com
Project Insight has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your complaint, please contact or visit JAMS (https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-or-safe-harbor-claim) for more information or to file a complaint. In accordance with the Privacy Shield Principles, this binding arbitration option is available at no cost to you in order to address residual complaints not resolved by any other means.
For the purposes of this Policy, our "Services" refer to the Project Insight™ Website, Project Insight SaaS project portfolio and management solution. It does not include third-party products that you may choose to integrate with Project Insight products or services, such as third-party add-ons available in the Project Insight web application add-ons listing. Please refer to the privacy policies governing third-party add-ons prior to integrating with Project Insight and remove any add-ons if you object to the third-party’s use of your personal information.
Collected Information
We require customers who register to use the Services offered on our website to give us contact information, such as their name, company name, address, phone number, e-mail address, financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number and the number of users within the organization that will be using the Services.
At the time you express interest in attaining additional information, or when you register for the service, we may also ask for additional information, such as title, department name, fax number, or additional company information, such as annual revenues, number of employees, or industry. Customers can opt out of providing this additional information by not entering it when asked. Customers can update or remove their information at any time by logging into the Services and editing their information within the Administration section. Customers can view their updated profiles to confirm the edits have been made.
Project Insight uses the information that we collect to set up Services for individuals and their organizations. We may also use the information to contact customers to discuss customer interest in our company, the Services that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. Customers are asked to provide an email address when registering for the Service to receive a username and password. We may email information regarding updates to the Service or company, or may also send a customer newsletter.
We share information, including personal information, with our third-party service providers that we use to provide hosting for and maintenance of our Websites, application development, backup, storage, payment processing, analytics and other services for us. These third-party service providers may have access to or process your personal information for providing these services for us. We do not permit our third-party service providers to use the personal information that we share with them for their marketing purposes or for any other purpose than relating to the services they provide to us.
Our customers will be using the Services to host data and information ("Data"). Project Insight will not review, share, distribute, print, or reference any such Data except as provided in a Services Agreement, or as may be required by law. Individual records may at times be viewed or accessed only for providing customer support, research a suspected violation of a Services Agreement, or as may be required by law. Customers are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality and security of their user registration and password.
Project Insight may also collect certain information from visitors to, and customers of the website, such as Internet addresses. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our Services for continuous quality improvement. We may also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers and provide such information to third parties.
Cookies and other tracking technologies from your use of the Services
When you interact with your Services, we strive to make that experience easy and meaningful. When you come to your Services, our web server sends a cookie to your computer. Cookies are files that web browsers place on a computer's hard drive and are used to tell us whether customers and visitors have visited the website previously.
Standing alone, cookies do not identify you personally. They merely recognize your browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to us, either by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, or registering for a 'trial period,' you remain anonymous to us. Cookies come in two forms: session and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you have closed your browser or turned off your computer. They include such information as a unique identifier for your browser.
Project Insight uses session cookies containing encrypted or encoded information including your username and session ID. This information allows us to process your online transactions and requests. Session cookies help us make sure you are who you say you are after you have logged in and are required to use the Services. Project Insight uses persistent cookies that only we can read and use, to identify the fact that you are our customer or prior Project Insight website visitor (whatever the case may be). We are especially careful about the security and confidentiality of the information stored in persistent cookies. For example, we do not store account numbers or passwords in persistent cookies. Users who disable their web browsers' ability to accept cookies will be able to browse our website but will not be able to successfully use our Services.
We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Web browsers offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML5 and Flash to collect and store information. For further information on how to manage Flash LSOs please click here.
Log Files from use our Services
As is true with most websites and services, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol addresses, browser, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and click stream data as well as certain personal information such as user name, user email address and other information that may be included in open text fields. Our Services log files are subject to the same strict data security policies and procedures as apply to our Services. We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve the Services that we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or Services functionality.
Analytics information from your use of our Services
We collect analytics information when you use our Services to help us improve them. We partner with a third party to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third-party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on our website and other sites to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here (or if located in the European Union click here). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads and you will continue to receive generic ads.
In our Services, analytics information may consist of the feature and function of the Service being used, the associated domain name, the username and IP address of your Agent or End-User (which may include personal information if the personal information was incorporated into the username) and additional information required to detail the operation of the function and which parts of a Service are being affected. The analytics information we collect may include elements of Service Data related to the function the end-user is performing. As such, the analytics information we collect may include personal information or sensitive business information.
Communications with Project Insight
When you send an email or other communication to us, including support requests for our Services, we may collect the personal information that you provide us and may use it in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our Services.
When you send an email or other communication to us, including support requests for our Services, we may collect the personal information that you provide us and may use it to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our Services.
You and your agents may receive occasional marketing communications regarding our products and services. You can opt-out of receiving marketing communications. Please contact privacy@projectinsight.com or follow the unsubscribe instructions included in our marketing communications to opt-out.
Blogs and Public Forums
Our Services offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. Information provided in these areas are read, collected, and used by others who access them. You may request removal of your personal information from these pages by contacting privacy@projectinsight.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Subscriber Testimonials/Comments/Reviews/Feedback
From time to time, we post subscriber testimonials on our website that may contain personal information. We obtain your consent to post names along with your testimonials. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, contact us at marketing@projectinsight.net.
Referrals
If you choose to use our referral service to tell another person about our Services, we will ask you for that person's name and email address. We will contact this person inviting him or her to visit our website or speak to us on the phone and will store this information for sending emails, the tracking the success of our referral program and other marketing activities. Referred individuals can opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us by contacting us at marketing@projectinsight.net or following the unsubscribe instructions included in our marketing communications.
Other Submissions
We collect other information, including personal information, that you submit to our Services or as you participate in certain interactive features of our Services, participate in surveys, contests, promotions, sweepstakes, activities or events, apply for a job, request customer support, communicate with us via third-party social media sites or otherwise communicate with us. Any information, including personal information that you submit through our Services could be visible to the public unless submitted via a secure area in the Services.
Social Media
Our Services include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and the Share This button, a Twitter Tweet This button, etc. or interactive mini-programs that run on our Services. These features may collect your Internet protocol address, which page you are visiting on our Services, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy statement of the company providing it.
Single Sign-On
You can log into some of our Services using single sign-in services. These services will authenticate your identity, provide you the option to share certain personal information (such as your name and email address) with us. Some of these services give you the option to post information about your activities on our Services to your profile page to share with others within your network.
Third-Party Sites
The Services may contain links to other websites. These websites could contain links that users input in the system as well. Project Insight is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other websites. Customers and visitors will need to check the privacy statements of these other websites to understand their policies. Customers and visitors who access a linked site may be disclosing their private information. It is the responsibility of the user to keep such information private and confidential.
How We Use Personal Information
General Uses:
We use the personal information that we collect for a variety of purposes. To
Provide, operate, maintain, analyze, improve and promote our Services and tailor our Services to our subscribers' needs;
Enable you and your end users to access and use our Services;
Process and complete transactions, and send you related information, including purchase confirmations and invoices;
Communicate with you, including responding to your comments, questions, and requests; providing customer service and support;
Provide you with information about services, features, surveys, newsletters, offers, promotions, contests and events;
Provide other news or information about us and our select partners; and sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Services and for marketing or advertising purposes;
Investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to our Services, and other illegal activities; and
For other purposes about which we notify you.
Analysis of our Websites and Services
As indicated above, we use the information we collect (including log and configuration data) to understand how our Services are being configured and used, how they can be improved, and to develop new services, features and functionality.
Sharing Personal Information
Third-party service providers
We share information, including personal information, with our third-party service providers (such as credit card processors, managed hosting providers, sub-processors of Service Data, and technology partners) to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and other services that we use to operate our Services and maintain a high-quality user experience. We do not permit our service providers to use the personal information that we share with them for their marketing purposes or for any other purpose than the services they provide to us.
We are responsible for the processing of personal received from the EU and then transferred to a third party acting as an agent on our behalf.
We remain liable in accordance if third-party agents that we engage to process such personal data on our behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Privacy Shield Principles, unless we prove that we are not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage. If you wish to limit or restrict the use or sharing/disclosure of your personal information, you can email us at privacy@projectinsight.com.
Other Services:
You may choose to make use of Other Services in conjunction with our Services. Other Services are third-party products, applications, services, software, products, networks, systems, directories, websites, databases and information which our Services link to, or which you may connect to or enable in conjunction with the Services, including, without limitation, Other Services which may be integrated directly into your account to which you grant access privileges to your account. When access is granted, certain information in your account is shared with the third party, including personal information. Project Insight does not control the policies and procedures of these Other Services even though the Other Services may be available through our Services. This Policy does not cover the collection or use of information, including personal information, by Other Services, and we urge you to consider the privacy policies governing these Other Services.
Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests:
We disclose personal information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may also share such information if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Service Agreement(s), or as otherwise required by law.
In accordance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Project Insight is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC).
Security
Our Services have security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the data under our control. Please read our Cloud Security Statement for details.
Opt-Out Policy
Project Insight offers its visitors and customers a means to choose how we may use information provided. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering Services, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about sharing your information with third parties, send us a request specifying your new choice. Simply send your request by email to privacy@projectinsight.com or easily unsubscribe using the link provided in each email.
Accessing, Updating & Removing Your Information
Customers maintain the right to access, update or change registration information by editing the user(s) or organization record. Some updates and removal procedures will require customer administration rights to the Services and may further require assistance from Support Services when deactivation of a user account or organization is required. Accounts managed by organizations and account administrators may be controlled by that organization and/or administrator as to how information is retained and deleted. To update a user profile or organization record, log on to your Service to do so. To update billing information, please call 949-476-6499.
Additional Information
Business Transactions
Project Insight may assign or transfer this Policy, and your account and related information and data, including any personal information, to any person or entity that acquires all our or substantially all our business, stock or assets of, or with whom we merge.
Questions
Any questions regarding this Policy should be directed to privacy@projectinsight.com.
LegalCustomer AgreementAcceptable Use PolicyCloud Security StatementAuthorized UsersPrivacy PolicyProfessional Services Agreement	Reporting Copyright and Trademark ViolationsThird Party Code
